{
    "id": "d25b42472c3342a5bbac389303e2c4f2",
    "title": "Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She is very …………………… and he is very short.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "tall",
                "long"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "88a1db59d24948ff97be73baec9553a1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t know how …………………… he is.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "old",
                "young"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2ac50ff2050b4008a3eb9ce7a37a0556"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is twenty-three years ……………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "old",
                "young"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e403124a3c774eff96d48a27768090f1"
        },
        {
            "question": "We use scales to measure how …………………… things are.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "light",
                "heavy"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "557084717c9d4d37987fd67770181182"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the …………………. of a football field?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "length",
                "height"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "990332a1d1e84edc8a40149415c9f29c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is six feet …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "tall",
                "high"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "37885d9d19f14b69ba1294b65e941503"
        },
        {
            "question": "How ………………….. is he?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "tall",
                "high"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0f5fe7d0f2c84bbd91c39817566df869"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has got beautiful ………………….. legs.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "tall",
                "long"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9a0e1aef9823467f83905288ee73b59b"
        },
        {
            "question": "That tree is about 60 feet ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "tall",
                "high",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ca656c61b4294a31b990459d1703a67d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The garden has got very ………………… walls.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "high",
                "tall",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6ea01505b838441aa5ed0c5730ceef7b"
        }
    ]
}